Guide to the Cornell University Glee Club Records, 1884-2014
Cornell University Glee Club Records, 1884-2014
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Glee Club records, 1884-2014
37-6-2399
Cornell University Glee Club
16 cubic ft.
Correspondence, programs, scrapbooks, photographs, notebooks, recordings, miscellany.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, programs, scrapbooks, photographs, notebooks, recordings, and miscellany concerning the Cornell University Glee Club, including the complete managerial papers from 1929 to 1980.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Founded as the Orpheus Glee Club in 1868, the Cornell University Glee Club (CUGC) is the oldest student organization on campus. One of the premier male choirs in the country, the ensemble performs a wide variety of repertoire, frequently traveling domestically and internationally. Past international concert tours have visited Mexico, the Soviet Union, Southeast Asia, Eastern Europe, China, Venezuela, and Brazil. Since 1889, the Club has been under the leadership of a number of notable directors.
For more information, visit www.gleeclub.com.
CHRONOLOGY
1889-1921 Hollis Ellsworth Dann
1921-1942 Eric Sydney Dudley
1942-1945 John Marinus Kuypers
1945-1946 Paul John Weaver
1946-1957 Thomas Brodhead Tracy
1957-1995 Thomas Andrew Sokol
1995-2012 Scott Arthur Tucker
2012-2013 John Rowehl (Interim director)
2013-Present Robert Isaacs
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes bound managerial papers, correspondence, and financial papers for every year from 1929 to 1976 (excluding war years), scrapbooks, photographs, programs, notebooks, recordings, songbooks, and miscellany concerning the Cornell University Glee Club (CUGC), its managers, directors, members, and alumni. Includes materials related to directors, managers, and advisory council members.
Also, scrapbooks (1954-55); USSR/England tour (1960-61); publicity and managerial records (1951-65); and an LP album, "Cornell music," consisting of music of the Glee Club, the Cornell chimes, and the Cornell Concert Band. Also microfilmed minutes and a poster for a Glee Club concert in the Philippines.
Contact the Glee Club Historian with questions.
PARTIAL LIST OF CORRESPONDENTS
Directors
Hollis E. Dann
Eric S. Dudley
John M. Kuypers
Thomas A. Sokol
Thomas B. Tracy
Paul J. Weaver
Graduate Managers
Romeyn Berry
R. Selden Brewer
J. Duncan Sells
Allan H. Treman
Advisory Council Members
Robert A. Beck
Foster M. Coffin
George L. Coleman
Robert G. Engel
H. Victor Grohmann
Howard A. Heinsius
Richard C. Howard
Austin H. Kiplinger
Richard H. Lee
Stanley A. Malinowski, Jr.
Deane W. Malott
Paul L. McKeegan
John C. Nicolls
John S. Ostrom
William H. Seymour
W. Barlow Ware
Bruce W. Widger
G. Wallace Woodworth
Theodore P. Wright
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Cornell University--Societies, etc.; Cornell University--Students.; Choirs.; Choral societies.; Concert programs--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Music.; Music--Societies, etc.; Singers.; Broadsides.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
See also: Box 26 of Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, #21-37-2227, for photos of the Glee Club Asia tour in January 1989. Job # 1434, 16 rolls, each with many frames, taken by Gordon Webb.
See also collection #3-13-2843 for a VHS tape of the 1989 Asia Tour.
See also Cornell University Songs and Sheet Music collection, #47-6-2124, http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMA02124.
See also Leslie Fenner memorabilia, #37-5-4158.
See also the Music Library for many recordings.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Photographs
Subseries A. Band and Orchestra
Box 18
Subseries B. Banjo and Mandolin Clubs
Boxes 4, 18
Subseries C. Miscellaneous Ensembles
Box 18
Subseries D. Individuals and Small Groups
Box 18
Subseries E. Combined Clubs
Boxes 4, 18
Subseries F. Glee Club
Boxes 18
Series II. Scrapbooks
Boxes 3, 5-6, 24-26, 30
Series III. Audio-Visual Materials
Boxes 3, 5, 26-29, 31
Series IV. Managerial Papers
Subseries A. Eric S. Dudley Years
Boxes 1-2
Subseries B. Interim Years
Box 2
Subseries C. Thomas B. Tracy Years
Boxes 2, 7
Subseries D. Tracy and Sokol Years
Box 7
Subseries E. Thomas A. Sokol Years
Box 7-17
Subseries F. Miscellaneous Papers
Box 17
Series V. Publications
Boxes 3, 18
Series VI. The Hangovers
Boxes 29-32
Series VII. Other Material
Subseries A. Printed Material
Boxes 17, 18, 21, 23
Subseries B. Posters and Fliers
Boxes 30, 32
Subseries C. Sheet Music
Boxes 30
Subseries D. Glee, Banjo and Mandolin Club Programs
Boxes 19-21
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Photographs
  - Two negative proof sheets of a photo of the Arts Quad showing Boardman Hall and the Clocktower (Box 18)
  - Subseries A. Band and Orchestra
    - Marching (Cadet?) Band, 1916-1917 Thirty members plus drum major Robert C. Pooley and George Coleman (Box 18)
    - Ithaca Band and Orchestra by E. D. Evans Eleven members (Box 18)
    - Orchestra by E. D. Evans Nine members (Box 18)
    - Orchestra by Howes (with smaller copy), 1910 Thirty-seven members and George Coleman (Box 18)
    - Orchestra in Bailey Hall Fifty-four members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Orchestra in Bailey Hall Seventy-one coed members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Orchestra in Bailey Hall by Trevor Teele Seventy-two coed members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Orchestra in Bailey Hall by Trevor Teele Eighty coed members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Orchestra in Bailey Hall, 1940-1941 Seventy coed members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Orchestra photocopy in Bailey Hall, 1940-1941 Seventy coed members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - High School Orchestra and Chorus from Tennesee Includes George Coleman as director (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Subseries B. Banjo and Mandolin Clubs
    - Banjo and Mandolin Club of 1890-1891 by Howes, Ithaca, NY, 1891 Fifteen members (Box 4)
    - Banjo and Mandolin Club of 1892-1893, 1893 Fifteen members (Box 4)
    - Banjo and Mandolin Club, 1893 Eighteen members (white ties) (from Spencer L. Adams) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Mandolin Club Forty-two members (white ties) and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Mandolin Club by Troy (3 copies) Sixty-one members (white ties) and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Mandolin Club by Troy Forty-four members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Mandolin Club by Troy, November 6, 1927 Thirty-nine members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Mandolin Club by Troy, 1928-1929 Thirty-eighty members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Mandolin Club (2 copies), 1929-1930 Twenty-eight members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Instrumental Club, 1939 Thirty-two members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Instrumental Club (plus 2 photocopies), 1940-1941 Twenty-seven members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Subseries C. Miscellaneous Ensembles
    - Sage Chapel Choir (2 copies), 1940-1941 Eighty+ members and directors (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Unknown women's ensemble, 1940-1941 Twenty-three members (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Drama members applying make-up, 1940-1941 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Strange actor in poses (2 different) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Group photographs, 1940-1949 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Photographs, 1950-1959 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Mexico Tour photographs, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Europe Tour photographs, 1960s (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - USSR, England, Denmark, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - England Tour, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Asia Tour, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Asia Tour, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Germany Tour, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Eastern Europe Tour, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Photographs, 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Photographs, 1980-1989 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Tour to Spain, France, Switzerland, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Photographs, 1990-1999 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Photographs, 2000s (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - China Tour Photo CDs, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Glee Club Photo CD, 39260 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Supreme Court Photo CD, photographs, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Photos of Thomas Tracy, Undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Photos of Thomas. A. Sokol, Undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Glee Club Photos, Undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Glee Club Guest Conductors, Undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - A large number of photos, 1966 (Box 22)
    - Group photo from Dudley Years (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Group photo from Dudley Years, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Group Photo from War Years (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Group Photo from War Years (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Group Photo, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Scott Tucker's Farewell Reunion Concert Photos, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Scott Tucker's Farewell Reunion Concert Photos, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Glee Club Photo, 1926 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Glee Club Photo, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - George Coleman Portrait, 1901 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Photo of Members with Vienna Choir Boys, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Subseries D. Individuals and Small Groups
    - Quartet by Troy (2 copies) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Octet Includes R. T. Banks Grad (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Octet J. S. Hower Jr. '28, R. T. Banks Grad, W. R. Morgan '27, H. L. Merriman '28, R. W. Kinne '28, C. E. Wallace '27, N. C. Northup '29, J. B. Moreton '29 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Octet W. R. Morgan '27, R. T. Banks Grad, W. C. Sutherland '28, N. C. Northup '29, Chase, Brauner, Young, F. M. Pelton '28 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Octet by Troy (3 copies) A. J. McAllister '28, T. K. Powers '30, G. D. Ogden '28, T. Hoffer '28, W. C. Sutherland '28, J. S. Hower Jr. '28, J. B. Moreton '29, F. M. Pelton '28 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Octet (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Glee Club Quintet Piano player, two singers, two banjo players (including Allan H. Treman) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Quartet and Banjo Duet (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Banjo quartet by Troy (2 copies), Dec. 5, 1926 A. M. Laidlaw '27, C. F. Spindler '27, D. Lewis '28, A. R. VanArsdale '28 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Banjo quartet by Troy (2 copies), Dec. 1, 1927 E. R. VanArsdale '28, W. E. Bachman '29, H. S. Brown '29, A. F. Sulla Jr. '29 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Banjo quartet by Troy H. S. Brown '29, W. E. Bachman '29, E. R. VanArsdale '28, A. F. Sulla Jr. '29 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Banjo duet (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Banjo duet (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Banjo player in clown outfit by Troy (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Small band (2 copies) Piano, trumpet, saxophone, drums, and George Coleman on violin (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - B. D. Chamberlain, Leader by Troy (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Dexter S. Kimball Jr. '27, Leader by Troy (2 copies) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Truman A. Lacey, President by Troy (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Wistar Ambler, Manager (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Roger W. Kinne '28, Soloist by Troy (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Roger W. Kinne '28, Soloist (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - C. R. Hanson (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - L. A. Goodwin (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Individual (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Two individuals (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Two individuals goofing around by Troy (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Subseries E. Combined Clubs
    - Glee, Banjo and Mandolin Club by Howes, Ithaca, NY (multiple different), ca. late 1800s (some without director, some with instruments, some with Hollis Dann) (Box 4)
    - Glee, Banjo and Mandolin Club of 1891-1892 by Howes, Ithaca, NY, 1892 Twenty-one members and Hollis Dann (Box 4)
    - Combined Clubs by Troy Ninety-eight members (white ties) and George Coleman, Hollis Dann (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Combined Clubs One hundred fifteen members (white ties) and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Combined Clubs by Troy Ninety-four members and George Coleman, Eric Dudley (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Combined Clubs One hundred four members and George Coleman, Eric Dudley (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Combined Clubs by Troy (3 copies), Nov. 6, 1927 One hundred four members and George Coleman, Eric Dudley (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Combined Clubs by Troy (2 copies), 1928-1929 Ninety-one members and George Coleman, Eric Dudley (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Combined Clubs, 1929-1930 Eighty-five members and George Coleman (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Subseries F. Glee Club
    - First Glee Club, Oct. 16, 1869 Beebe, Wilmot, Van Wagenen, Raymond, Ramsey (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Second Glee Club, 1880-1881 Seventeen members (white ties and mortarboards); includes list of members (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Glee Club, 1893 Twenty-three members (white ties) and Hollis Dann (from Spencer L. Adams) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Glee Club by Troy Fifty-six members (white ties) and Eric Dudley (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Glee Club by Troy, Nov. 6, 1927 Fifty-six members and Eric Dudley (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Glee Club, 1928-1929 Fifty-six members and Eric Dudley (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Glee Club Sixty-six members and Eric Dudley (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Series II. Scrapbooks
  - Cornell Glee Banjo and Mandolin Clubs Scrapbook, 1915-1917 Large photograph of dog labeled "Barnum," group photograph, concert programs, 24th and 25th annual Christmas trip booklets, newspaper clippings (including articles about Hawaiian composer R. Alex Anderson), publicity, etc. (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook for 62nd Senior Week Show by the Cornell Musical Clubs, 1935 Photographs, concert programs, newspaper clippings, publicity, etc. (Box 3)
  - Cornell Musical Clubs Scrapbook, 1935-1936 Photographs, concert programs, newspaper clippings, publicity, etc. (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook for "Here We Are Again" Tour, 1947-1948 Group photograph, photographs, newspaper clippings, press releases, tour booklet, concert programs, miscellaneous papers from 1948. (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook for Cornell Musical Clubs Christmas Trip, 1937 Newspaper clippings, publicity. (Box 3)
  - Cornell Musical Clubs Scrapbook, 1940-1941 Newspaper clippings, concert programs (including WHCU dedication), tour booklet. (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook for "From Blue Cayuga" Spring Tour, 1955 Batavia, Cleveland, Toledo, Milwaukee, Chicago, St. Louis, Cincinnati, Akron. Newspaper clippings, concert programs, tour booklet, etc. (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook for USSR/England Tour, 1960-1961 Photographs, concert programs, newspaper clippings, press releases, tourist booklets/pamphlets, menus, etc. (Box 5)
  - Scrapbook for Midwest/Mexico Tour "From Far Above," 1954 Atlanta, Houston, Mexico City, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Denver, Tulsa, Topeka, Davenport Photographs, concert programs, posters, newspaper clippings, telegram from Kansas governor Edward F. Arn, etc. (Box 6)
  - Scrapbook for England Tour, 1963 Photographs, concert programs, posters, newspaper clippings, etc. (Box 6)
  - Kirk Birrell Programs and Pictures, 1950 (Box 25)
  - USSR Tour Photos, 1961 (Box 24)
  - European Tour, 1961 (Box 25)
  - Assorted Photos, 1965 (Box 24)
  - Publicity Photographs, 1965 (Box 24)
  - Press Book, 1966 (Box 24)
  - Bacolod City Performance, 1966 (Box 24)
  - Japan Press Book, 1966 (Box 24)
  - T. Willis Diary- Asia Tour, 1966 (Box 24)
  - Philippines Scrapbook, 1966 (Box 25)
  - St. Paul College, Manila, 1966 (Box 25)
  - Far East Tour, 1966 (Box 24)
  - Far East Tour Scrapbook, 1966 (Box 29)
  - Philippines Press Releases 1, 1966 (Box 25)
  - Philippines Press Releases 2, 1966 (Box 25)
  - Photo Book, 1966 (Box 29)
  - Newspaper articles (Box 29)
  - Newpaper Article Collection (Gray), 1967 (Box 25)
  - Photo Album (Green), 1970 (Box 25)
  - Florida Tour, 1981-1982 (Box 24)
  - England Tour, 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Photo Book, 1962-1993 (Box 24)
  - Flower Photo Book, 1999 (Box 24)
  - Tour Programs and Daily Sun, 1973 (Box 26)
  - Glee Club Publicity, 1967 (Box 26)
  - Asia Tour Book 1, 1966 (Box 26)
  - Asia Tour Book 2, 1966 (Box 26)
  - Asia Tour Book 3, 1966 (Box 26)
  - Asia Tour Book 4, 1966 (Box 26)
  - Scrap book pages, Eric Kjellmark, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Series III. Audio-Visual Materials
  - Parents Weekend Performance, 7" reel April 1965, TR. 7806
  - Columbia Records recording of "Cornell" and "Alma Mater," ca. 1913, Available online here: https://archive.org/details/78_alma-mater_cornell-glee-club_gbia0012275a (Box 3)
  - Columbia Records recording of "Cornell" and "Alma Mater" (II), ca. 1913 (Box 3)
  - Geographical Fugue, VHS, V-808 and V-5521 (Box 5)
  - Senior Week Concert, May 29, 1993; tr-10893 (Box 26)
    Cassette
  - Fall Concert, October 27, 1990; tr-10894 (Box 26)
  - Songs of Cornell, tr-10895 (Box 26)
  - Midwest Tour, 1993; tr-10896 (Box 26)
  - Lincolnshire Posy-Grainger, From a Dark Millennium-Schwantner, from Symohony No. 1 "Jeremiah-Bernstein, May 1, 1999; tr-10897 (Box 26)
  - Senior Week Concert, 1999; tr-10898 (Box 26)
  - England Tour and Lynn Festival, 1982; tr-10899 (Box 26)
  - Fall Concert, 1992; tr-10900 (Box 26)
  - Bruckner's Mass in E Minor, March 6, 1993; tr-10901 (Box 26)
  - Fall Concert, November, 1993; tr-10902 (Box 26)
  - Fall Concert, September 17, 1994; tr-10903 (Box 26)
  - The Wellesley Choir and the Cornell University Glee Club, March 5, 1995; tr-10904 (Box 26)
  - Senior Week Concert, May 27, 1995; tr-10905 (Box 26)
  - Homecoming Concert, 1995; tr-10906 (Box 26)
  - Southwest Tour, 1996; tr-10907 (Box 26)
  - Brahm's ein deutches Requiems, 1996; tr-10908 (Box 26)
  - Homecoming Concert, 1996; tr-10909 (Box 26)
  - Samite: ONE VOICE a benefit concert for AIDS, 1997; tr-10910 (Box 26)
  - Senior Week Concert, 1997; tr-10911 (Box 26)
  - Homecoming Concert, 1997; tr-10912 (Box 26)
  - Senior Week Concert, 1998; tr-10913 (Box 26)
  - Homecoming Concert, 1998; tr-10914 (Box 26)
  - Tour of Eastern Europe, 1972; SR-9801-9802 (Box 28)
    Record
  - Nabuchodonosor, 1964; SR-9803 (Box 28)
  - Brahms Nanie, Op. 82, March 22, 1970; SR-9804 (Box 28)
  - Schubert's Mass in A-flat, D. 678, March 7, 1979; SR-9805 (Box 28)
  - England Tour, June 1, 1963; SR-9806-9807 (Box 28)
  - Songs of Cornell, 1970-1979; SR-9808-9809 (Box 28)
  - Songs of Cornell, 1960-1969; SR-9810-9811 (Box 28)
  - Spring Concert, 1975; SR-9812 (Box 28)
  - Berlioz Requiem under Karel Husa, December 10, 1966; SR-9813 (Box 28)
  - Concert Tour of England, 1979; SR-9814 (Box 28)
  - Verdi Requiem, 1974; SR-9815 (Box 28)
  - Missa Solemnis under Karel Husa, March 10, 1965; SR-9816 (Box 28)
  - far above..., 1956-1957; SR-9817-9818 (Box 28)
  - Cornell University Glee Club under Thomas Sokol, undated; SR-9819 (Box 28)
  - Beethoven's Symphony No. 9 with the Philadelphia Orchestra under Eugene Ormandy, 1962-1963; SR-9820 (Box 28)
  - Cornell Men's Glee Club, 1954-1955; SR-9821-9822 (Box 28)
  - Cornell Men's Glee Club, 1951; SR-9823, SR-9836 (Box 28)
  - Saint John's Passion, undated; SR-9824 (Box 28)
  - Brahms Rhapsody and Stravinsky's Oedipus Rex, 1968; SR-9825, SR-9837 (Box 28)
  - Cayuga's Waiters, 1951-1952; SR-9826 (Box 28)
  - Columbia Record of Alma Mater and Cornell, 1913; SR-9827, SR-9835 (Box 28)
  - Cayuga's Waiters, undated; SR-9828 (Box 28)
  - Glee, Banjo, and Mandolin Clubs, undated; SR-9829 (Box 28)
  - Cornell Glee Club, 1949; SR-9830 (Box 28)
  - Tour Advertisement Record, 1978; SR-9831 (Box 28)
  - History of the Cornell Alma Mater, undated; SR-9832-9833 (Box 28)
  - Nani, Carmina Burana, SR-9834 (Box 28)
  - Cornell Men's Glee Club, 1957; SR-9838 (Box 28)
    Records
  - Royal College of Music Concert, January 15, 1987; tr-10915 (Box 27)
    Reel to Reel
  - CBS Cavalcade of Christmas Music, December 1, 1987; tr-10916 (Box 27)
  - Requiem by Maximilian Albrecht, April 14, 1963; tr-10917-10918 (Box 27)
  - Music of Bach and Reicha, April 20, 1974; tr-10919-10920 (Box 27)
  - Cornell Alumni Association Glee Club Songs of Cornell Records, 1950-1959; SR-9789-9796 (Box 27)
    Record Collection
  - Cornell Alumni Association Glee Club and Waiters Songs of Cornell Records, 1950-1959; SR-9781-9788 (Box 27)
  - Cornell Glee Club in 1950, 1950; SR-9797-9800, 9839-9842 (Box 27)
  - Geographical Fugue, Concert Tour of Asia 1988-1989, 1989; V-9136 (Box 27)
    VHS
  - Geographical Fugue, Concert Tour of Asia 1988-1989, 1989; V-9137 (Box 27)
  - Geographical Fugue, Concert Tour of Asia 1988-1989, 1989; V-9138 (Box 27)
  - San Diego News, 2005; V-9139 (Box 27)
  - Segments from Asia Video, 1989; V-9140 (Box 27)
  - Cornell Glee Club, Cornell Chimes, Cornell Concert Band, SR-6226 (Box 28)
  - Cornell Glee Club, CBS Television, F-1625 (Box 29)
  - The Alumni Glee Club, F-1626 (Box 29)
  - Cornell Records 1950, SR-9775 (Box 31)
  - The Cornell Men's Glee Club of 1951-52 (4 records), SR-9776-9779 (Box 31)
  - Glee Club, SR-9843-9844 (Box 31)
- Series IV. Managerial Papers
  - Subseries A. Eric S. Dudley Years
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1923 Also contains "Manual on Musical Clubs Concerts" with instructions for hosting. (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1926-1927 (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1929 Also contains concert programs. (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1930 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1931 Also contains 37th annual tour booklet, letter from Romeyn Berry inviting Allan Treman to join the Musical Clubs Council. (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1932 Also contains programs for the Women's Glee Club. (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1933 (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1934 Also contains newspaper clippings, drafts of Constitution. (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1935 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1936 Also contains newspaper clippings, quartet photograph, letter from Mrs. Roosevelt. (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1937 Also contains concert programs, photograph of concert hall. (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1939 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1940 Also contains photographs of students in dorm and concert halls. (Box 2)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1941 Also contains newspaper clippings, papers regarding the approaching war and Dudley's approaching retirement. (Box 2)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1942 Also contains papers regarding the politics of the change in directors, the war, and the draft situation. (Box 2)
  - Subseries B. Interim Years
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1943 Also contains agreement by Musical Clubs Council to suspend operations, guide to managing the Glee Club. (Box 2)
  - Subseries C. Thomas B. Tracy Years
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1946 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs, tour booklet, information about the appointment of Tracy as director. (Box 2)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1947 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs (Spring concert dedicated to Eric Dudley). (Box 2)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1948 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs, group photographs. (Box 2)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1949 Also contains newspaper clippings, individual photograph (of soloist?), written Alma Mater sheet music. (Box 2)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1950 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 2)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1951 Also contains newspaper clippings, checkbooks from Tompkins County Trust Company, correspondence regarding proposed Brazil tour. (Box 2)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1952 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 2, Folder 1-10)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1953 (Box 7)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence (continued), 1953 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 7)